Guide to the Fletcher Nelson Papers, 1901-1981 UA.29.02.0226
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sermon Notes, 1926-1966; 2
  - Keeping Serene in a Chaotic World, 1944 (Box 3)
  - The Might of the Mite, Finances, 1944-1947 (Box 3)
  - Walking in the Truth, 1944-1946 (Box 3)
  - Dear Dad, 1944-1949 (Box 3)
  - Half Cures, 1941-circa 1944 (Box 3)
  - On Entering the Kingdom, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Living Together as Citizens of the Kingdom, circa 1944 (Box 3)
  - The Sons of the Kingdom, circa 1944 (Box 3)
  - The Assets of the Kingdom, circa 1944-1949 (Box 3)
  - It Must Come That Way, 1944-1948 (Box 3)
  - Concerning the Collection, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Overcoming Sorrow, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Expectations of Minister and People, 1940-circa 1944 (Box 3)
  - Liberty and Loyalty, 1944-1947 (Box 3)
  - Fireside Religion, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Thoughts for Thanksgiving, 1944-1948 (Box 3)
  - Our Crusade for Christ, 1944 (Box 3)
  - People Who Missed Christmas, 1944 (Box 3)
  - When Sorrow Comes, 1944-1945 (Box 3)
  - I'd Form Good Habits, 1945 (Box 3)
  - What Think Ye of Christ, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Church Has a Job Too, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Why I Joined the Church, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Foundations of Sapphires, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Jesus Christ, What Does He Mean to You?, 1943-circa 1945 (Box 3)
  - Protestantism, 1945-1948 (Box 3)
  - The Plain Man and the Future, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Our Mothers and Our Homes, 1945-1949 (Box 3)
  - Vision and Life, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Through Jesus Christ Our Lord, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Does the Church Matter?, 1945-1948 (Box 3)
  - The Wonderful Christ, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Let's Be Sensible!, circa 1945-1949 (Box 3)
  - On Being Tempted to be Christian, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Religion Will Help!, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Some Hesitations of American Christianity, 1945-1949 (Box 3)
  - America Owes Christianity Something, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The World Needs a New Citizen, 1945-1947 (Box 3)
  - Thanksgiving Thoughts, 1945 (Box 3)
  - That You May Live, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Impossible Christ, 1945 (Box 3)
  - So Little Time!, 1945-1949 (Box 3)
  - A Watch Night Common Service, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Field is the World, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Humility!, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Dance of Redemption, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - On Accepting Life, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Three Crosses on Calvary, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Look In! Look Out! Look On!, circa 1946 (Box 3)
  - Easter to Me, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Civilization is Sustained Here, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - Sin and the Average Man, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Religion of Jesus, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Religion in Personal Daily Life, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Value of Life, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - The Christian and His Sorrows, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - A Christian Conscience Concerning Alcohol, 1945-1949 (Box 3)
  - The Achievement of Fidelity, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Concerning Worshiping Together, 1946-1949 (Box 3)
  - The Majesty of the Commonplace, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Mission: The Arrival in Bethlehem (Series: Gospel in Art), 1946 (Box 3)
  - On Reading the Bible, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - Burne-Jones: The Star of Bethlehem Gospel in Art, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Prejudice!, 1947 (Box 3)
  - God Has a Plan for Your Career, circa 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Marks of a Christian Home, 1946-1947 (Box 3)
  - Simon, His Beat, and Jesus, 1947-1966 (Box 3)
  - It Is Hard to be Christian, 1947 (Box 3)
  - When Christ Controls, 1947 (Box 3)
  - The Author of Salvation, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
  - A Look at the Cross, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Munkacsy: Christ Before Pilate, circa 1947 (Box 3)
  - Your Inevitable Cross!, 1947 (Box 3)
  - The Importance of Little Things, 1947-1966 (Box 3)
  - The Sacredness of Life, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Choose Life, 1947-1966 (Box 3)
  - On Seeking Life, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Our New Morality, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Some Thoughts on Giving, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
  - The Methodist Church and Institutional Education, 1947 (Box 3)
  - The Child and Church, 1948 (Box 3)
  - There is No Permanent Victory, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
  - Methodism in Today's World, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
  - The Fellowship of the Concerned, 1948 (Box 3)
  - Being Tough on Oneself, 1948 (Box 3)